I'm sayin' bodies are honest
You, the intellect, even come too
Hey
Oh so mightily you lecture me. Though
you secretly want to blend with me
To be honest I know
I won't be loved truly
Hey
Kiss me one last time
I won't ask for anything else
just saying, the body is honest. - shikiura (ver. Sou)
Yo
You c
You can'
You can't e
You can't eras
You can't erase th
You can't erase the me
You can't erase the memor
You can't erase the memories
You can't erase the memories wit
You can't erase the memories with m
You can't erase the memories with me
An
And y
And you
And you sa
And you said
And you said yo
And you said you'd
And you said you'd lik
And you said you'd like m
And you said you'd like me fo
And you said you'd like me forev
And you said you'd like me forever
You can't erase the memories with me
Y
You
You can't erase the memories with me
And you said you'd like me forever
You we
You can't erase the memories with me
And you said you'd like me forever
You were
You were t
You can't erase the memories with me
And you said you'd like me forever
You were the
You were the fir
You can't erase the memories with me
And you said you'd like me forever
You were the first
You were the first to
You can't erase the memories with me
And you said you'd like me forever
You were the first to tak
You were the first to take m
You were the first to take mine
I
I can
I can't wa
I can't wait an
I can't wait any mo
I can't wait any more
I can't wait any more  G
I can't wait any more  Get
I can't wait any more  Get me
I can't wait any more  Get me we
I can't wait any more  Get me wet
I
I saw
I saw yo
I saw you in
I saw you in the
I saw you in the cit
I saw you in the city w
I saw you in the city we s
I saw you in the city we spen
I saw you in the city we spent to
I saw you in the city we spent toget
I saw you in the city we spent together
H
Hap
Happi
Happily
Happily ta
Happily talki
Happily talking
Happily talking to
Happily talking to oth
Happily talking to other
Happily talking to other gi
Happily talking to other girls
I'
I'll
I'll k
I'll ki
I'll kill
I'll kill th
I'll kill the
I'll kill them
I'll kill them al
I'll kill them all f
I'll kill them all for
I'll kill them all for you
S
So
So h
So ho
So hold
So hold m
So hold me
So hold me ti
So hold me tigh
So hold me tight fo
So hold me tight fore
So hold me tight forever
I'm sayin' bodies are honest
You, the intellect, even come too
Hey
Oh so mightily you lecture me. Though
you secretly want to blend with me
To be honest I know
I won't be loved truly
Hey
Kiss me one last time
I won't ask for anything else
(15 seconds interval)
I'm sayin' bodies are honest
You, the intellect, even come too
Hey
Oh so mightily you lecture me. Though
you secretly want to blend with me
To be honest I know
I won't be loved truly
Hey
Kiss me one last time
I won't ask for anything else